[Music]
writers of Destiny your attention
please no keep writing it's your only
job just also pay
attention ever since our dear euphrasia
revealed herself as the elemental master
of wind something I personally supported
from the very beginning we've learned
our writing is not the only way we can
influence the world we can also uh what
is it again Marcus we can do things
Master writer take actions other than
writing yes a bold new idea and the
first thing we want to do is make this
place more fun so let's spitball fun
ideas hit
me I don't know
Bagels uh I think bigger oh oh Merlo
t-shirt day mucoid hat Mondays yes
love seriously all anyone wants is
bagels uh lend me a spare quill
something's wrong with mine a quill that
won't
write wait mine isn't
writing why did you stop working we want
you to work the same amount just be
funner about it we're trying to but our
quills aren't working this has literally
never happened before and ever maybe
it's the
ink it's not the
ink it is said that when the writers of
Destiny can no longer write something is
coming something so Dreadful even
Destiny herself cannot stop
[Music]
it
summon you frasia the cloud kingdom is
an extreme Peril let us hope it is not
already too late in me and not so much
to together we will
R
[Music]
we
behind look everyone isn't it
beautiful and now that Empress Beatrix
is gone we can make Imperium all we've
dreamed it could be together Public
Gardens sustainable power sources more
than one flavor of tea and will open the
city to everyone from Ninjago and
Beyond the sky is the
liit what is
[Music]
that
help so you've been having dreams about
these Warriors in Wolf masks they've
been so terrifying I haven't been able
to sleep for weeks I thought they were
just nightmares but after fighting those
wolf masks last night we now know
they're actually Visions H visions of
terrible dangerous to come and they
always end with something called a Blood
Moon then I wake up
screaming drink up Sir my dear mummy's
very own feted swamp tea recipe it'll
calm your jangled
nerves that looks so
good what's with the
Flies that's now you know it's
working compared to that tea my panic
attack doesn't seem so bad see told you
it would do wonders even if they are
Visions it doesn't mean that what you
see is definitely going to happen right
we're in charge of our own destiny we
weren't so in charge last night my wonky
Spinjitsu is no match for that new
Elemental Master don't be so hard on
yourself Aaron you were caught off guard
next time all us Ninja will be there
yeah where there's an elemental master
of smoke there's an elemental master of
Fire H you're right I don't know what
I'm so scared about Ninja never
quit o except for maybe this
tea O pardon me so this Elemental Master
took the Mallet he stole to Lord Ross
what does Raz want with it we know it
can't be for something good well I can
think of one place to look for
[Music]
answers I've heard fulan the guy who
owns this place is kind of sketchy since
you two know the people of Crossroads
better than we do I feel like you'll
have more success getting information
from him which means Aaron we got to
stay tough when we interrogate him why
wouldn't I ah cuz you're so nice you
believe anything anyone tells you
remember when creel convinced you she
was a robot I really didn't think a
human could dance like
that the
Ninja can I help
you what can you tell us about the
ancient Mallet that was taken from your
shop last
night yeah I don't know anything about
that cool thanks for for your
time we know a mallet was stolen from
this place fulan you don't want your
property back we could help but we need
to know why someone would want it who
knows look people bring me old stuff I
sell it I can't research everything in
this place like what's this a door stop
a helmet there's no way to know I'd love
to catch the Ruffian that broke into my
place but I have a business to run
H let's go he's definitely hiding
something are you sure I mean he seemed
sincere Aaron I love you buddy but you
got to realize that not everyone tells
the
truth any chance you can get us up to
that rooftop there
ahuh
I got to get one of those
[Music]
Grapplers pantro the ninja were just
here gross sheesh that's a little
hurtful they asked about the Mallet I
told them I knew nothing of course but
consider this a warning the ninja might
come calling wow I'm really bad at
spotting
Liars huh H might be time for me to take
a little vacation
[Music]
then that graffiti on the wall behind
her I know it I drew it I was young and
bored but let's
go there it is your noodle graffiti
that's a cat why are there meatballs on
its face those are the eyes
scanning zero cats detected in this
image uh yeah okay we didn't come to
dunk on my old art H's Hideout has got
to be around here
somewhere let's do a search in a pattern
expanding out
from oh hey Ninja nice to meet you I'm
just cleaning up this nonv valuable junk
as part of a city beautification plan
and uh uh uh the best part is none of
these Antiquities were looted and all of
them are super
legal looks like you're not really
buying that so magic
attack okay turns out that item was not
actually magical my mistake but hey
killer butterfly SW
so not the killer kind hard to know
sometimes but how about psychic or
blast I see the problem now it's just a
door up sorry I'm kind of new at this
looted ancient artifacts game are you
done trying to fight us did I even start
really look I just find artifacts and
sort of NAB them it's it's not not like
I steal from actual people am I in
trouble depends on how well you answer
our questions the Mallet you gave fidan
what's its purpose that thing rumor has
it that's the Mallet to something called
The Gong of
shattering gong of
shattering it's a myth from the wildness
supposedly someone can hit the gong with
that Mallet and it releases their dark
energies ooh
are we believing
her I can't tell anymore would I
lie yes I totally would but right now
I'm not this is just what I
heard apparently everyone has some good
inside them but if you're wearing a
weird wolf mask and then hit the gong
with the Mallet it shatters the goodness
inside you a wolf mask weird right and
once you shatter your goodness you not
only gets stronger apparently you can
learn all kinds of evil
things what kinds of evil things
fighting techniques mystical Powers all
the stuff your goodness was holding you
back from if you believe in that
mystical cursy
[Music]
garbage so you buy hro story a Gong that
shatters goodness it matches my vision
exactly welcome to the monastery of
Spinjitsu how can we peral what are you
doing
[Music]
here you
frasia ninja we need your help what
happened could those be please no
no too easy and we didn't even need to
use the gong of shattering the gong must
be used judiciously now Jordana to the
archives maybe you jerks haven't heard
but the cloud kingdom is now protected
by the elemental master of
wind
looks like you got the wind knocked out
of
you
huh my
I get to the
[Music]
ninja I tried to fly to your Monastery
but came up short that's where peral
found me the cloud Kingdom archives is a
bunch of Scrolls and research what would
Lord RZ need to learn about the blood
moon it has to have something to do with
it if my Visions are real I know the
blood moon is important and very very
bad
seriously this grapple rules I traded
for an elemental power don't get
impatient Aaron every ninja has a
different
path it's so quiet I think you mean
creepy be prepared for
anything
the writers of Destiny thank goodness
you're
okay maybe not the most
okay they are translating from some
ancient language but not one I recognize
it's a language that
looks evil how can a language look evil
trust me it
does
thank you
ninja you're frasia you're
alive
barely what happened it was
awful this archive is our most precious
resource we'll defend it with our lives
you
foes no you won't I need you alive
for now one of the reasons I introduced
a curse into your scroll worms
aai you curse the
[Music]
worms
gross but kind of awesome gross do those
Scrolls have anything to do with the
blood moon Raz wouldn't he couldn't that
sounds like a yes the Blood Moon Rises
once every few Millennia in the wildness
and on this rarest of events there is an
Arcane ritual that can be performed to
resurrect The Forbidden five they sound
a little intimidating they are the
Forbidden five were once Elemental
Masters thousands of years ago they
discovered evil Powers no other
Elemental Master could stop they
conquered their realm and destroyed all
who stood in their way nothing could
stop them it seemed impossible but a
Mystical Force arrived from the East and
banished them beyond all the Realms
forever the fives discoveries teachings
even their language have been banned for
centuries if Raz can unlock their
secrets and then enact the ritual of the
blood moon he could bring them
back I why is everyone so serious this
is simple we just stop Ros before he
even knows we're here might be too late
for
[Music]
that ninja
go
try all you want Ninja but you'll never
be as powerful as us are you not seeing
this we're kicking wolf mask butts
you've got your facts all wrong whoever
you are what I'm Jordana your Nemesis
you've been dreading our next encounter
huh oh wait are you that girl who is in
my class back in Imperium why are you
way out
here you're about to find
out it's the Maladin gong guess we're
about to find out if shattering goodness
is a real
thing okay that is looking pretty
real this is the sound from my
visions we're with you Lloyd together
and we're ready for
this there's no tech for my Elemental
tech power then just use Spinjitsu oh
right
sorry you were right Sora my Visions
don't matter we're in charge of our own
destinies
[Music]
and we're ending your occupation of the
cloud Kingdom now Ross I beg to differ
Cinder I heard there's a new Elemental
master of smoke you know I thrashed the
last one
right we know what you're doing trying
to uncover anent Secrets but they were
forbidden for a
reason tried no I've succeeded I have
begun to unlock real power behold What
Becomes of an elemental master who has
studied the Lost teachings of the
Forbidden
VI
is that some kind of Spinjitsu it is a
corrupted advanced form of your beloved
fighting technique that has been long
banned forgotten shut I
spin I've never even heard of this who
cares let's
fight
come on he can't stop all of
[Music]
us
you'll pay for
that
wallf fires hurt
bad
Cinder finish them
off our only logical move now is to
retreat but ninja don't Lloyd there's no
other way if we want to defeat Ros we
have to get out of here and regroup come
on come
on
[Music]
how can we stop bra with that kind of
power we'll find a way Lloyd Master woo
trained us well he did Nia but he didn't
train us for this who can teach us how
to stop shatter
spin the Cloud Kingdom and all the Dark
Secrets within now belong to me our
journey to the blood moon continues The
Forbidden VI shall rise
[Music]
again